- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[whimsical nautical music]
[异想天开的航海音乐]
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
We are going
- [笑]
我们要去
to have so much fun!
玩得开心！
A weekend in a cabin
in the woods
在小屋里度过一个周末
在树林里
with the Gal Pals!
和 Gal Pals 一起！
all: Gal pals!
全体：姐妹们！
Yeah!
是的！
- [exclaims]
- Oh, a krabby patty.
- [惊呼]
- 哦，蟹肉饼。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Perfect.
- Ugh.
- 完美的。
- 呃。
- The engine needed greasing.
- 发动机需要润滑。
- [exclaims]
Yah!
- [惊呼]
啊！
Congratulations, Mrs. Puff!
恭喜你，普芙女士！
Your boat and trailer
just got hitched!
您的船和拖车
刚刚结婚！
[laughs]
[笑]
[all laughing]
[Karen beeping]
[全都笑了]
[凯伦嘟嘟声]
- Hmm, I wonder what's keeping
our newest Gal Pal?
我们最新的 Gal Pal？
[thundering steps]
【雷霆脚步】
- This is gonna be so funny.
- 这会很有趣。
The Gal Pals will obviously
try to prank the newbie,
Gal Pals 显然会
尝试恶作剧新手，
but this newbie
is gonna prank them right back.
但是这个新手
马上就要恶作剧他们了
[laughs]
- Boo!
[笑]
- 嘘！
Who likes eggs?
[laughs]
谁喜欢鸡蛋？
[笑]
- Not now, SpongeBob.
- 海绵宝宝，现在不行。
Wait until you're around
the campfire.
等到你在身边
篝火。
And you're supposed
to act scary, not lame.
而你应该
表现得可怕，而不是跛脚。
- Oh, scary.
Got it!
- 哦，可怕。
知道了！
Wait until the fire
then make with the scary.
等到火烧起来
然后与可怕的人一起做。
[goofy exclamations]
[愚蠢的感叹]
[wails, grunts]
[哀号，咕噜声]
- Keep working on it.
- 继续努力。
- Here comes
our newest member!
- 来了
我们的最新成员！
all: Gal Pals!
Yeah!
全体： 好朋友们！
是的！
[all chattering, laughing]
[大家叽叽喳喳，大笑]
- Here, let me get your bag.
[grunts]
- 来，我来拿你的包。
[咕哝]
[all grunting]
[全都咕哝]
- Ow.
[grunts]
- 噢。
[咕哝]
[door creaks, closes]
[门吱吱作响，关上]
Nice and cozy.
美好而温馨。
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
all: ♪ We're Gal Pals ♪
全体：♪ 我们是好朋友 ♪
♪ And, yes, we shall
conquer the world one day ♪
♪ 而且，是的，我们将
总有一天会征服世界♪
♪ We're no sea bunnies,
we're smart and funny ♪
♪ 我们不是海兔，
我们又聪明又有趣♪
♪ And we demand equal pay ♪
♪ 我们要求同工同酬 ♪
♪ We'll shout "Gal Pals"
right into your ear canal ♪
♪ 我们会喊“Gal Pals”
直接进入你的耳道♪
♪ And bang it on a drum ♪
♪ 然后敲鼓 ♪
♪ We're sweet and nice,
but take our advice ♪
♪ 我们又可爱又友善，
但请接受我们的建议♪
♪ Cross us and you'll be chum ♪
[creature bellows]
♪ 与我们联系，你会成为好朋友的 ♪
[生物咆哮]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
[creature grunting, munching]
[生物咕噜声、咀嚼声]
♪ ♪
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
- Ooh, this is gonna be
so much fun!
- 哦，这将会是
太有趣了！
We're gonna have
a real adventure
我们将会有
一次真正的冒险
with our newbie,
aren't we, ladies?
和我们的新手一起，
女士们，我们不是吗？
[all laughing deviously]
[Karen beeps]
[大家都奸笑]
[凯伦嘟嘟声]
- [laughs nervously]
- [紧张地笑]
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
[laughing deviously]
[狡猾地笑]
♪ ♪
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[wails, grunts]
[哀号，咕噜声]
[babbling, groaning]
[胡言乱语，呻吟]
Whoa!
[yells, grunts]
哇！
[喊叫，咕哝]
Huh?
啊？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Where am I?
我在哪里？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Huh?
啊？
All right, I'll just sit tight
and wait to hear from Pearl.
好吧，我就坐稳了
等待珍珠的消息。
I've got the trailer,
我有预告片
so there's plenty of food
and blankets.
所以有很多食物
和毯子。
[glum music]
[忧郁的音乐]
[mud burbling]
[泥浆潺潺]
- [growls]
Barnacles!
- [咆哮]
藤壶！
Now what am I gonna do?
现在我该怎么办？
Hey, a peanut!
嘿，一颗花生！
A lucky peanut!
幸运花生！
Mm, I'm not gonna go hungry
out here.
嗯，我不会挨饿的
在这里。
I'm gonna survive!
[voice echoes]
我会活下去！
[声音回声]
Wait a minute,
I can't eat this peanut.
等一下，
我不能吃这个花生。
You're my lucky peanut.
[giggles]
你是我的幸运花生。
[咯咯笑]
I've got a lucky peanut!
[voice echoes]
我有一个幸运花生！
[声音回声]
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
- Here we are.
- 我们到了。
- Uh-oh, looks like
we lost something.
- 呃哦，看起来像
我们失去了一些东西。
- [gasps]
Oh, no, my backpack!
- [喘气]
哦，不，我的背包！
This is the worst thing
that could ever happen!
这是最糟糕的事情
这可能会发生！
- Aww, there, there, sweetie.
- 哇哦，那里，那里，亲爱的。
It's just a backpack.
We can buy you a new one.
这只是一个背包。
我们可以给你买一件新的。
It's not like losing a friend.
这不像失去朋友。
- [whimpers]
She must be psychic.
- [呜咽]
她一定是有灵性的。
- Aww, heck,
we'll just have to rough it!
- 哇，哎呀，
我们只能艰难地度过！
[mice squeaking]
[creature snarling]
[老鼠吱吱声]
[生物咆哮]
[substance burbles, splats]
[物质沸腾、溅出]
All right, gals,
let's not just hang here
好吧，姑娘们，
我们不要只是挂在这里
like mama's washing!
就像妈妈洗衣服一样！
Time to gussy up the place!
是时候打扮一下这个地方了！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
Hmm.
唔。
- Good thing we have
a Texas tornado
- 好东西我们有
德克萨斯州龙卷风
among the Gal Pals.
Gal Pals 中。
Who knew you could
use a jellyfish as a recharger?
谁知道你可以
用水母当充电器？
[jellyfish buzzing]
[electricity zapping]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[电击]
- Oh, yeah.
[sighs]
- 哦，是的。
[叹气]
- Yep, nature always provides.
- 是的，大自然总是提供。
- Hey, where's the newbie?
- 嘿，新人在哪里？
- Oh...
- 哦...
Oh, please, SpongeBob,
be all right.
哦，拜托，海绵宝宝，
没事吧。
[phone line ringing]
[电话铃声响起]
- [goofy babbling]
- [愚蠢的胡言乱语]
I'm Sponge-zan
of the brine apes!
我是海绵赞
盐水猿！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[yelps, groans]
[尖叫声、呻吟声]
Ooh!
[grunts]
哦！
[咕哝]
[phone rings]
[电话铃声]
Oh, my lucky peanut's ringing.
[goofy exclamation]
哦，我的幸运花生响了。
[愚蠢的感叹]
Hello?
你好？
[ringing continues]
[铃声继续]
Oh.
[grunts]
哦。
[咕哝]
Shell-lo?
[laughs]
贝壳洛？
[笑]
- SpongeBob!
- 海绵宝宝！
Oh, thank Neptune
you're still alive.
哦，谢谢海王星
你还活着。
- Don't worry, Pearl,
I'm still gonna do the prank.
- 别担心，珍珠，
我还是要搞恶作剧。
I just have to find your cabin.
我只需要找到你的小屋。
Are there any landmarks
I can head to?
有没有什么地标
我可以去吗？
- Um, well,
there are a lot of trees.
- 嗯，好吧，
有很多树。
- Trees, perfect!
- 树，完美！
I'll just follow the trees.
我就跟着树走吧。
Are you sure you didn't ring,
too, lucky peanut?
你确定你没响吗
还有，幸运花生？
Hello, hello?
Ugh, bad reception.
喂，喂？
呃，接待不好。
No peanut bars.
没有花生棒。
[peanut beeping]
[花生嘟嘟声]
Eh.
呃。
Follow the trees!
跟着树走！
Follow the trees,
follow the trees,
跟随树木，
follow the trees...
跟随树木...
[voice fades]
[声音渐弱]
[all laughing]
- [sighs]
[全都笑了]
- [叹气]
[all chuckle]
[全场笑声]
- [slurps] Oh, this kelp cocoa
is delicious.
- [咕噜咕噜]哦，这个海带可可
很好吃。
[scanner whirs, beeps]
[扫描仪嗡嗡作响，嘟嘟声]
- Yeah, my sensors indicate
an agreeable flavor.
- 是的，我的传感器表明
令人愉快的味道。
- Okay, Gal Pals,
- 好吧，姑娘们，
it's time to initiate
our newest member.
是时候开始了
我们的最新成员。
[sinister music]
[险恶的音乐]
- [whines]
- [grunts]
- [哀嚎]
- [咕哝]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- You are now a Gal Pal.
- 你现在是一个 Gal Pal。
- That's it?
Just this necklace?
- 就是这样？
就这个项链吗？
No swats or parading around
in my PJs?
禁止殴打或四处游行
在我的睡衣里？
No trying to scare me
with urban legends?
别想吓唬我
与都市传说？
- Why would we do that?
- Yeah, we like you.
- 我们为什么要这么做？
- 是的，我们喜欢你。
- We haven't had
a fourth member
-我们没有过
第四名成员
since that incident
with Flibberty Gibbet.
自从那次事件以来
与 Flibberty Gibbet 一起。
I--
- Puff!
我——
- 噗！
Shh.
嘘。
- Who's "Slippery Giveth"?
- “滑溜溜的给予”是谁？
- Oh, Flibberty Gibbet.
-哦，轻浮绞刑架。
She was the fourth member
of our group.
她是第四位成员
我们组的。
We had a fight with her
years ago
我们和她吵架了
几年前
right here at this very cabin
就在这个小屋里
one dark and stormy night.
一个漆黑而暴风雨的夜晚。
[thunder crashes]
[雷霆轰鸣]
- We don't even remember
what the fight was about.
-我们甚至不记得了
这场战斗是关于什么的。
- It sure was a humdinger
of an argument!
- 这确实是一个嗡嗡声
一个争论！
- She went bananas
- 她发疯了
and vowed to destroy
并发誓要摧毁
any and all Gal Pals.
任何和所有的 Gal Pals。
[imitates slicing]
[模仿切片]
- Then she just ran off
into these woods!
- 然后她就跑掉了
进入这些树林！
- Some say
she's still out there,
- 有人说
她还在外面，
all hot-headed
and waiting to get her revenge.
头脑发热
并等待着为她报仇。
[wails]
[哀号]
- That's her pendant
you're wearing.
- 那是她的吊坠
你穿着。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
"Flibberty Gibbit"?
“轻浮的吉比特”？
[screams, grunts]
[尖叫声、咕哝声]
[hollers]
[喊叫]
Why did you give me that?
你为什么给我那个？
Why did you take me here?
你为什么带我来这里？
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
[laughs]
[笑]
Thanks, gals, you got me.
谢谢，姑娘们，你们抓住了我。
But I knew
you were gonna prank me.
但我知道
你本来想恶作剧我的。
- Sure you did.
- [laughs]
- 当然你做到了。
- [笑]
You should have seen your face.
- [growling]
你应该看到你的脸。
- [咆哮]
- We got you good!
- 我们让你很好！
- [laughs]
Mm, Gal Pals.
- [笑]
嗯，加尔朋友。
[tree crashes]
[all scream, whimper]
[树倒塌]
[所有人尖叫，呜咽]
- [gasps] What was that?
- [喘气] 那是什么？
- 'Kay, you can stop
trying to scare me.
- '凯，你可以停下来了
试图吓唬我。
I know Flipperty Giblets
is a prank.
我知道 Flipperty 内脏
是一个恶作剧。
- Flibberty Gibbet
is partly true.
- 轻浮绞刑架
部分属实。
- She was a Gal Pal.
- 她是一个 Gal Pal。
We did have a fight with her.
我们确实和她吵过架。
- And she did run off
into these woods.
- 她确实逃跑了
进入这些树林。
- Wait, that was all the parts!
- 等等，这就是所有的部分了！
[crashing]
[崩溃]
- [growls, snarls]
- [咆哮，咆哮]
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
- Quick, let's hide
in the cabin!
- 快点，我们躲起来
在机舱里！
- Wait, it--it's okay.
It's only SpongeBob.
- 等等，这——没关系。
这只是海绵宝宝。
I asked him to make noise
and prank you.
我请他发出声音
并恶作剧你。
All right, SpongeBob,
you can come out!
好吧，海绵宝宝，
你可以出来了！
I'm canceling the prank!
我要取消恶作剧了！
- [stifled laughter]
- [压抑的笑声]
There's another tree.
还有一棵树。
[pants]
And another tree.
[裤子]
还有另一棵树。
Wow, following the trees
really works.
哇，跟着树走
真的有效。
Tree, tree, tree, tree.
树，树，树，树。
- So, SpongeBob thinks
he can prank us, huh?
- 所以，海绵宝宝认为
他可以恶作剧我们，是吧？
We'll prank him right back.
我们马上就恶作剧回来。
We can rig up the cabin
with trap doors,
我们可以组装小屋
带有活板门，
flying ghosts,
and a thousand cadavers
飞行的幽灵，
和一千具尸体
in a zombie ballroom!
在僵尸舞厅里！
Ooh, what am I saying?
哦，我在说什么？
- Let's scale it down a smidge.
- 让我们把它缩小一点。
- Yeah, let's hide
behind this tree
- 是啊，我们躲起来吧
在这棵树后面
and scream when he shows up.
当他出现时尖叫。
[all giggle]
- You coming, Pearl?
[大家咯咯笑]
- 你来吗，珀尔？
- Well, I'm certainly not
staying by myself
- 嗯，我当然不是
我一个人呆着
here in the dark.
在黑暗中。
[all giggle]
- Shh, he's coming.
[大家咯咯笑]
- 嘘，他来了。
Wait for it.
等等吧。
Now!
[all scream]
现在！
[所有人尖叫]
[all exclaim]
- [roars]
[所有人惊呼]
- [咆哮]
all: Flibberty Gibbet!
[all scream]
所有人： 愚蠢的绞刑架！
[所有人尖叫]
- It's her!
- 是她！
Oh, s-she looks like she's been
in the woods too long!
噢，她——她看起来好像已经
在树林里呆太久了！
- I have a plan.
- 我有一个计划。
We'll run out the back door
and into Puff's boat.
我们会从后门跑出去
Count of three.
数到三。
One, two, three!
[all screaming]
一二三！
[所有人尖叫]
- [roars, screams]
- [咆哮，尖叫]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Let's go!
- 我们走吧！
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
- Rawr!
- 劳尔！
Hmm?
唔？
Huh.
[goofy babbling]
呵呵。
[胡言乱语]
- No, no!
- SpongeBob!
- 不，不！
- 海绵宝宝！
- Don't go in!
- Oh, hello.
- 别进去！
- 哦，你好。
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- Gal Pals,
we have to save SpongeBob!
- 加尔朋友们，
我们必须拯救海绵宝宝！
[whining]
all: Gal Pals.
[抱怨]
全部： Gal Pals。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- Wow!
- [growls]
- 哇！
- [咆哮]
- Ooh, another pinecone
on a stick!
- 哦，另一个松果
在一根棍子上！
I love it.
我喜欢它。
- [growls]
- Wow!
- [咆哮]
- 哇！
- I'm gonna get one of these
for each of the Gal Pals.
- 我要买其中一件
对于每个 Gal Pals 来说。
all: Huh?
- [laughs]
全体：啊？
- [笑]
It's only a cabin-to-cabin
country sales lady.
这只是一个舱对舱
乡村销售小姐。
Not Flibberty Gibbet at all.
根本不是轻浮的绞刑架。
- Did someone say my name?
- 有人说了我的名字吗？
Hi, gals!
all: Flibberty Gibbet!
嗨，姑娘们！
所有人： 愚蠢的绞刑架！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[whimsical music]
[异想天开的音乐]
- I--I just wanted to say
all's forgiven!
- 我--我只是想说
一切都被原谅了！
- Hey, wait!
- 嘿，等等！
You'll need my lucky peanut!
你需要我的幸运花生！
all: Gal Pals!
[all grunt]
全体： 好朋友们！
[全都咕哝]
[all groan]
[全都呻吟]
♪ ♪